<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="${descVersion}">
	<author>${author}</author>
	<version>${version}</version>
	<title>
		<en>${title}</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[
Have you ever felt like you can't join two fields because of a rock that's right in the middle of them, or you can't build a shed because of some objects that take up space?
These will no longer be problems thanks to "Map Objects Hider", this mod will let you permanently remove decorative objects and placeable items on your maps.
You can open the mod settings panel by pressing RSHIFT + R

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Added settings (RSHIFT + R)
- Fixed issue with dynamic objects
- Improved loading to prevent hidden objects from reappear after mod updates

Be careful:
- Not all object types can be removed.
- If you change the hierarchy of objects on the map (for example by making changes from GIANTS Editor) some objects may reappear and have to be removed again.
- If a mod map is not built correctly, removing some trees may cause the above problem.
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[
Hatten Sie schon einmal das Gefühl, dass Sie zwei Felder nicht miteinander verbinden können, weil ein Felsen genau in der Mitte liegt, oder dass Sie einen Schuppen nicht bauen können, weil einige Objekte Platz wegnehmen?
Mit "Map Objects Hider" ist das kein Problem mehr, denn mit diesem Mod können Sie dekorative Objekte und platzierbare Gegenstände auf Ihren Karten dauerhaft entfernen.

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Einstellungen hinzugefügt (RSHIFT + R)
- Problem mit dynamischen Objekten behoben
- Verbessertes Laden, um zu verhindern, dass versteckte Objekte nach Mod-Updates wieder auftauchen

Aber Vorsicht!
- Nicht alle Objekttypen können entfernt werden.
- Wenn Sie die Hierarchie der Objekte auf der Karte verändern (z.B. durch Änderungen im GIANTS Editor), können einige Objekte wieder auftauchen und müssen erneut entfernt werden.
- Wenn eine Mod-Map nicht korrekt aufgebaut ist, kann das Entfernen einiger Bäume das oben genannte Problem verursachen.
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[
Avez-vous déjà eu l'impression que vous ne pouvez pas joindre deux champs à cause d'un rocher qui se trouve en plein milieu, ou que vous ne pouvez pas construire un hangar à cause de certains objets qui prennent de l'espace ?
Ces problèmes ne se poseront plus grâce à "Map Objects Hider", ce mod vous permettra de supprimer définitivement les objets décoratifs et les objets pouvant être placés sur vos cartes.

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Paramètres ajoutés (RSHIFT + R)
- Correction d'un problème avec les objets dynamiques
- Amélioration du chargement pour empêcher les objets cachés de réapparaître après les mises à jour du mod

Faites attention :
- Tous les types d'objets ne peuvent pas être supprimés.
- Si vous modifiez la hiérarchie des objets sur la carte (par exemple en effectuant des changements à partir de l'éditeur GIANTS), certains objets peuvent réapparaître et doivent être supprimés à nouveau.
- Si une carte de mod n'est pas construite correctement, la suppression de certains arbres peut causer le problème ci-dessus.
]]>
		</fr>
	</description>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="lib/utility/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="lib/rmod/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="lib/rset/Main.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="mapObjectsHider.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="playerExtension.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="events/objectHideRequest.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="events/hideDecollideNode.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="events/deleteSplitShapeEvent.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>

	<actions>
		<action name="MAP_OBJECT_HIDER_HIDE" axisType="HALF" />
	</actions>

	<inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="MAP_OBJECT_HIDER_HIDE">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_h" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>

	<l10n>
		<text name="input_MAP_OBJECT_HIDER_HIDE">
			<en>Hide a map object</en>
			<fr>Masquer un objet sur la carte</fr>
			<de>Ausblenden eines Kartenobjekts</de>
			<es>Ocultar un objeto del mapa</es>
			<pl>Ukrywanie obiektów na mapie</pl>
			<ru>Скрыть объект</ru>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_HIDE">
			<en>Hide (%s)</en>
			<fr>Masquer (%s)</fr>
			<de>Ausblenden (%s)</de>
			<es>Ocultar (%s)</es>
			<pl>Ukryj (%s)</pl>
			<ru>Скрыть (%s)</ru>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_SELL">
			<en>Sell (%s)</en>
			<fr>Vendre (%s)</fr>
			<de>Verkaufen (%s)</de>
			<es>Vender (%s)</es>
			<pl>Sprzedaj (%s)</pl>
			<ru>Продать (%s)</ru>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_DELETE">
			<en>Delete (%s)</en>
			<fr>Supprimer (%s)</fr>
			<de>Löschen (%s)</de>
			<pl>Usuń (%s)</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_dialog_text">
			<en>Are you sure you want to hide %s?</en>
			<fr>Etes-vous sûr de vouloir masquer %s ?</fr>
			<de>Sind Sie sicher, dass Sie %s ausblenden möchten?</de>
			<es>¿Está seguro que quiere ocultar %s?</es>
			<pl>Jesteś pewien, że chcesz ukryć %s?</pl>
			<ru>Вы уверены, что хотите скрыть %s ?</ru>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_sell_dialog_text">
			<en>Are you sure you want to sell %s?</en>
			<fr>Etes-vous sûr de vouloir vendre %s ?</fr>
			<de>Sind Sie sicher, dass Sie %s verkaufen möchten?</de>
			<es>¿Está seguro que quiere vender %s?</es>
			<pl>Jesteś pewien, że chcesz sprzedać %s?</pl>
			<ru>Вы уверены, что хотите продать %s ?</ru>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_delete_split_shape_dialog_text">
			<en>Are you sure you want to remove this tree/log?</en>
			<fr>Etes-vous sûr de vouloir supprimer cet arbre ?</fr>
			<de>Möchten Sie diesen Baum / dieses Protokoll wirklich entfernen?</de>
			<pl>Jesteś pewien, że chcesz usunąć to drzewo/kłodę?</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_dialog_title">
			<en>Map Objects Hider</en>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_mod_settings_title">
			<en>Map Objects Hider</en>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_hide_confirm_enabled">
			<en>Objects confirm dialog</en>
			<fr>Message de confirmation lors du masquage</fr>
			<de>Objekte bestätigen Dialog</de>
			<es>Diálogo Confirmación Objetos</es>
			<pl>Okno potwierdzania obiektów</pl>
			<ru>Диалог подтверждения</ru>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_hide_confirm_enabled_tooltip">
			<en>Whether to show a confirmation dialog before hiding an object (Highly suggested to leave it enabled)</en>
			<fr>Utilisation d'une confirmation lors du masquage (fortement conseillée)</fr>
			<de>Ob vor dem Ausblenden eines Objekts ein Bestätigungsdialog angezeigt werden soll (es wird dringend empfohlen, ihn aktiviert zu lassen)</de>
			<es>Si mostrar un cuadro de diálogo de confirmación antes de ocultar un objeto (se sugiere dejarlo habilitado)</es>
			<pl>Czy pokazywać okno dialogowe potwierdzenia przed ukryciem obiektu (zdecydowanie zaleca się pozostawienie go włączonego)</pl>
			<ru>Следует ли показывать диалоговое окно подтверждения перед скрытием объекта (Настоятельно рекомендуется оставить его включённым)</ru>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_sell_confirm_enabled">
			<en>Placeable confirm dialog</en>
			<fr>Message de confirmation lors de la vente</fr>
			<de>Platzierungen bestätigen Dialog</de>
			<es>Diálogo Confirmación Colocables</es>
			<pl>Okno potwierdzania obiektów placeable</pl>
			<ru>Отображаемый диалог подтверждения</ru>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_sell_confirm_enabled_tooltip">
			<en>Whether to show a confirmation dialog before selling a placeable</en>
			<fr>Utilisation d'une confirmation lors de la vente</fr>
			<de>Ob ein Bestätigungsdialog angezeigt werden soll, bevor ein Platzierungselement verkauft wird</de>
			<es>Si mostrar un cuadro de diálogo de confirmación antes de vender un colocables</es>
			<pl>Czy pokazywać okno dialogowe potwierdzenia przed sprzedaniem obiektu placeable</pl>
			<ru>Показывать ли диалоговое окно подтверждения перед продажей объекта</ru>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_split_shapes_confirm_enabled">
			<en>Trees confirm dialog</en>
			<fr>Message de confirmation lors de la suppression d'arbres</fr>
			<de>Bäume bestätigen Dialog</de>
			<pl>Okno potwierdzania drzew</pl>
		</text>
		<text name="moh_split_shapes_confirm_enabled_tooltip">
			<en>Whether to show a confirmation dialog before removing trees and logs</en>
			<fr>Utilisation d'une confirmation lors de la suppression d'arbres</fr>
			<de>Gibt an, ob ein Bestätigungsdialogfeld angezeigt werden soll, bevor Bäume und Protokolle entfernt werden</de>
			<pl>Czy pokazywać okno dialogowe potwierdzenia przed usunięciem drzew i kłód</pl>
		</text>
	</l10n>

</modDesc>
